Guide to the Les K. Wright papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010.
Wright, Les K. papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Walter, Cornelia, 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Watson, Howard, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Webb, Link, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wehrle, Dale, 1994-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wehrle, Dale, 1994-2000 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
  - Wehrle, Dale, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 8b)
    Includes last will and testament of Leslie Wright, as well as Health Care Proxy forms and Power of Attorney forms
  - Wellman, BA, 1994-1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Welton, Richard (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Westin-Thomas, David, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Wetmore, Phil, 1989-2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - White, Peter, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Wheeler, Mark, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Wogrin, Carol, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Wolf, Joe, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Wood, Shelli, 1989-1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Wrights, 1989-2000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Wright, Marty and Ginny, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - To Billie Aul from Les K. Wright, 1972-2000 (Box 8, Folder 20-24)
  - To Ken Ratcliffe from Les K. Wright, 1982-1994 (Box 8, Folder 25-30)
  - Poetry sent by LKW to Billie Aul (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Photocopies of correspondence, poetry to/from Billie and Diane, 1974-1979 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Abrams, Brett, 2000 (Box 23)
  - Albert, Steve, 1999-2001 (Box 23)
  - Alexander, Jim, 1997-2002 (Box 23)
  - Alexander, John, 2000-2003 (Box 23)
  - Aloisi, Tom, 1999-2001 (Box 23)
  - Amplo, Bill, 2001-2003 (Box 23)
  - Anderson, Normund, 2000-2001 (Box 23)
  - Arnaboldi, Allan, 2002-2003 (Box 23)
  - Arning, Bill, 2001-2003 (Box 23)
  - Assmann, Jan, 2000 (Box 23)
  - Aul, Billie, 2000-2004 (Box 23)
  - Barela, Tim, 1996-1999 (Box 23)
  - Barnard, Sylvia, 2001-2004 (Box 23)
  - Bennett, Bryan, 2000 (Box 23)
  - Bergman, David, 2000 (Box 23)
  - Blanchard, Dennis, 2000-2003 (Box 23)
  - Brady, Will, 2000 (Box 23)
  - Broerman, Bruce, 2000-2003 (Box 23)
  - Brown, Lawrence, 1999-2002 (Box 23)
  - Burke, Michael, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Burrows, John, 2000-2003; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Byrne, Chris, 2002-2003 (Box 23)
  - Byrnes, Craig, 2001-2002 (Box 23)
  - Campbell, John, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Centrone, Paul, 2001 (Box 23)
  - Chappell, Urso, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Churchill, Dan, 2002 (Box 23)
  - Chvany, Peter, 2001-2003 (Box 23)
  - Cibuls, Juris, 2001-2002 (Box 23)
  - Coffey, Bob, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Comeau, Gary, 2000-2001 (Box 23)
  - Cox, Barth, 1999-2000 (Box 23)
  - Crosspoints, 1999-2003 (Box 23)
  - Cusick, Bob, 2001 (Box 23)
  - Dahir, Mubarak, 2001 (Box 23)
  - Darke, Alex, 2000-2002 (Box 23)
  - David (in Spain), 2001-2003 (Box 23)
  - De Cecco, John, 2002-2003 (Box 23)
  - Demers, Peter, 2000-2001 (Box 23)
  - De Mey, Pierre, 2001 (Box 23)
  - Dennison, Andy (and Toni), 2001-2002 (Box 23)
  - Dickemann, Jeffrey/Mildred, 2000-2004 (Box 23)
  - DiPaoli, John, 2002-2003 (Box 23)
  - Donahue, Bob, 2002-2003 (Box 23)
  - Donnellan, Brendan, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Doran, Rich, and David Plunkett, 2002 (Box 23)
  - Ebersole, Bob, 2002-2004 (Box 23)
  - Erikson, Carl, 2002-2003 (Box 23)
  - Eurobear (Michael Henke), 2000 (Box 23)
  - Farrar, Scott, 2004 (Box 23)
  - Floyd, Van Lynn, and Ron Triplett, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Follansbee, Don, 2001-2004 (Box 23)
  - Forester, Tom, 2000-2001 (Box 23)
  - Forrest (Bob MacIlwain), 2000-2003 (Box 23)
  - Fox, Lawrence, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Fritscher, Jack, 2001-2004 (Box 23)
  - Gampert, Richard, 1999-2000 (Box 23)
  - Ganczaruk, Sam, 2000-2004; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Gardiner-Scott, Tanya, 2000-2003 (Box 23)
  - Gardner, Al, 2000-2001 (Box 23)
  - Gescher, Gwen and Dieter, 2001-2003 (Box 23)
  - Gilgun, John, 2000-2003; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Glaser, Steve, 2001-2002 (Box 24)
  - Glessner, Dick and Sandy (Box 24)
  - Glover, Ken, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Gnaegi, Rene, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Goodman, Simon, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Gould, Mitch, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Green, Jamison, 2002 (Box 24)
  - Gustafson, Laura, 2001-2004 (Box 24)
  - Hallberg, Georg, and Peter Gethmann, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Harkins, Harry (Box 24)
  - Harper, Nildo, and James Mejeur, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Hazel, Dann, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Heasley, Robert, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hecox, Lance, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Heller, Jonathan, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Hendricks, John Milton, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Hernandez, Michael, 2002-2003 (Box 24)
  - Hess-Luttich, Ernest, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Heyl, Steve, and John Griffin, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Higgs, David, 2001 (Box 24)
  - Hill, Scott, 1997-1999 (Box 24)
  - Hillman, Hal, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Hirshberg, Bob, 2000-2002 (Box 24)
  - Hocking, Peter, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hoffman, Richard, 2002 (Box 24)
  - Holcomb, Dave, and Craig Johnson, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Holmes, Tim, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Hunt, Dan, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hurlbut, Tom, and Rick Rossi, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - Huzbears ring (David and Bryan), 2002-2003 (Box 24)
  - Hyslop, Seamus, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - Jobin, Vincent, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Jochum, Heinrich, 2001 (Box 24)
  - Johnson, Mark Scott, and Sanford Dole, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Jones, Jim W., 2000 (Box 24)
  - Kadour, Ric, and Chris Byrne, 2001-2003 (Box 24)
  - Kampf, Ray, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - Katz, Jonathan, 2001-2003 (Box 24)
  - Katzenberg, Mark, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Kaufman, Brian, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Kennedy, Hubert, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Kimmel, Michael, 1998-2001 (Box 24)
  - Klein, Steve, 2001-2003 (Box 24)
  - Kostas, 2001-2002 (Box 24)
  - Kristensen, Eric, 2001-2004 (Box 24)
  - Kwasigroh, David, 2000 (Box 24)
  - LaBonte, Jim, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - La Greca, Scott, 1999-2002 (Box 24)
  - Lan, Jeffrey, 2002-2003 (Box 24)
  - Landscapeguy1 ("Sean"), 2003 (Box 24)
  - Lattey, Elsa, 2001-2003 (Box 24)
  - Lawrence, E. Carl, 2000-2002 (Box 24)
  - Lazere, Arthur, 2001-2004 (Box 24)
  - Leap, Bill, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - Lefter, Chris, 2002 (Box 24)
  - Lehmann, Ruth, 2001-2003 (Box 24)
  - Lein, Eric, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - Libby, Tom, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Lijoi, Ernie, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Longino, Thom, 2001 (Box 24)
  - Lorey, Chris, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Lucies, Christopher, 2001 (Box 24)
  - Lutsky, Dan, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
  - Lyons, Eddy, 2002 (Box 24)
  - Maggard, Michael, 2002 (Box 24)
  - Marston, Brenda, 1998-2002 (Box 24)
  - Martin, Tim, 2001-2002 (Box 24)
  - Martinez, Guy and Rich, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Mason, Jim, 1999-2003 (Box 24)
  - Mass, Larry, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - Mauerman, Luke, 2001 (Box 24)
  - May, Steve, 2000 (Box 24)
  - McCann, Dr. Tom, 2001 (Box 24)
  - McCloskey, Danny, 2001-2003 (Box 24)
  - McDermott, George, 2002 (Box 24)
  - McDiarmid, Robert ("Waldenbear"), 2000-2003; 4 folders (Box 24)
  - McDiarmid, Robert ("Waldenbear"), 2003; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - McGillivray, Scott, 2001-2002 (Box 25)
  - McKeown, Edward, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Medina, David, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Mehler, Jill, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Michel, Dee, 2000-2002 (Box 25)
  - Molt, Cliff, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Moore, Bob, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Moran, John, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
  - Morris, Zac, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
  - Muller, Bob, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Nakazawa, Akira, 2002-2003 (Box 25)
  - Nimmons, Dave, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Noble, John, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
  - Norris, TJ, 2000-2002 (Box 25)
  - Nous, Nathan, and Ed Morris, 2000-2003 (Box 25)
  - Oakley, Tom, 2002-2003 (Box 25)
  - O'Dell, Brian, 2003 (Box 25)
  - O'Kelly, Erin, 2004 (Box 25)
  - Onofrietti, Joe, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Outcalt, John, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
  - Palmer, Bill, 2000-2003 (Box 25)
  - Parton, Jim, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Pate, Larry, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Patten, Bill, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Pazier, Ed ("Spike"), 2000 (Box 25)
  - Peterson, Gordon, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Piel, Barbara (Box 25)
  - Pollock, Ken, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Power, Bet, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Powers, Rychard, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Price, David, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Price, Tony, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
  - Pusztai, Bill, 2002-2003 (Box 25)
  - Ratcliffe. Ken, 2002-2003 (Box 25)
  - Reade, Alan, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
  - Reigns, Steven, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Rhine, Dont, 1997-2003 (Box 25)
  - Ricketts, Wendell, 2000-2003 (Box 25)
  - Riddle, Randy, 2001-2002 (Box 25)
  - Ridinger, Robert, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Rivera, "Larz" (J. Larry), 2002 (Box 25)
  - Roger ("RogUK"), 2003 (Box 25)
  - Russell, Walter, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Sahin, Mehmet Ali (Mali), 2001-2003 (Box 25)
  - Salinas, David, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Schneider, Richard, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Seele, Michael, and Donovan Miller, 1999-2001 (Box 25)
  - Senelick, Laurence, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Sherman, John, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
  - Sibal, Jim, 1999-2003 (Box 25)
  - Silverstein, Charles, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Sklute, John (Larry), 2001 (Box 25)
  - Somers, Peter ("TopCub0001"), 2000 (Box 25)
  - Steakley, Jim, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Steblein, Ed, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Stenoish, Jim, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
  - Stewart, Charles, 2002-2003 (Box 25)
  - Stone, Lynn, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Sullivan, Jay, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Suresha, Ron, 2000-2002 (Box 25)
  - Swinger, Martin, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Thompson, Dave, 2000-2003 (Box 25)
  - Tolley, Spencer, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Topping, John, 2002-2003 (Box 25)
  - Traynor, Gary, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Trust, Fred, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Turner, Gary, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
  - Urich, Billy, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Van Buskirk, Jim, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Ward, Bill, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Watson, Howard, 2000-2003 (Box 25)
  - Wehrle, Dale, 2000-2004 (Box 25)
  - Weisinger, Ken, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Wetmore, Phil, 2000-2003 (Box 25)
  - Whipple, Scott, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Wogrin, Carol, 2000-2002 (Box 25)
  - Wright, Lauren, 2000-2003 (Box 26)
  - Wright, Marty and Ginny, 2000-2003 (Box 26)
  - Youngman, Gordon, 2003 (Box 26)
  - Wright, Les - correspondence, phone log, office files [CD-ROM] and articles, 1997-2003; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Ad responses, 2003 (Box 26)
  - Unsorted correspondence, 1998-2003; 7 folders (Box 26)
  - Men's Resource Center of Western Massachusetts, 2001-2003; 2 folders (Box 26)
- Bailey, George (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Lawer, James (Box 53, Folder 2-3)
- Loose cards (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Broerman, Bruce (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
- Burrows, John, July 2010 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Series IV. Bear History Project
  - Bearskin Bend Lodge Journal, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Early Bear Tracks, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Bear Contests, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - The Bear History Project, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Bearskin Bend Lodge (BBL) 1-17, 1991-1999 (Box 3, Folder 67-77)
  - BHP (Bear History Project) Website v.2 Printout, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - BHP Newsletter #1-#6, #8, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 4-10)
  - BHP Contributors- Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 12-15)
  - Appalachian Bear Club, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Barenpost/ Bear Mail, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - B. C. Bears (Vancouver), 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Beach City Bears, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bear Back Calgary, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bear Buddies Toronto, 1995-1997, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bear Club of Japan, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Bear Pit (Denmark) Web Site, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Bear Club U. K., 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Bear Magazine, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Bears Down Under, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Bears LA- Bear's Growl, 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - Bears of Central Florida (Orlando), 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Bears of Manana, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Bears of Northeast (UK), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Bears of San Francisco, 1991-2005 (Box 9, Folder 17-19)
  - Bears of Southwest Florida, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Bears of the Old Pueblo, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Bears of Toronto, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Bear Paws of Iowa- Bear Facts- Bear Paws News, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Bears- Perth, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Bears San Diego, 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Bears Ventura, 1998-2004 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Berenfield Bears, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Berkshire Bears, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Berliner Bear, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Blackjack Bears of Las Vegas, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Bluegrass Bears, 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Brew City Bears, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Brisbears (Australia), 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
  - Buffalo Bears, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Bulk Toronto, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Burgh Bears, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Carolina Bear Lodge (Charlotte, NC), 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Cascade Bears Growl, 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Centurion (Alabama) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bears- The Growler, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Cleveland Bears, 1999-2005 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Dallas Bears, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Dallas Fort Worth Big Men's Club, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 44-45)
  - DC Bears, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Delaware Valley Bears, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Desert Empire Bears (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - East Coast Bears, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Fin- Bears, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Front Range Bears Grizzette, 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 51-52)
  - Girth and Mirth, Belgium, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Girth and Mirth of New England, 1993-2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Golden State Bears (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Great Lakes Bears, 1994-1999 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
  - GRUF Great Unshaven Faces (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Harbour City Bears (Sydney), 2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Heart of Texas Bears, 1995-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hoosier Bears, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Junction City Teddy Bears, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Kansas City Care Bears, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Kiwi K.U.B.S. Auckland, NZ, 1995-1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Las Vegas Bears, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Liberty Bears, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Lone Star Bears, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lone Star Gazette, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Long Island Bears, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Mainely Bears, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Mannheim Baren Treff, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Mid-Michigan Bears, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Minnesota Bears (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Monterey Bears, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Montreal Bears, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Monty Bears, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
  - Motor City Bears- Bear-in-Mind, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Music City Bears, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - New England Bears, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 28-30)
  - Mr. New England Bear, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - New Hampshire Bears, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - North Country Bears, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Northwest Bears, 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Northeast Ursamen, 1995-2000 (Box 10, Folder 35-37)
  - Oregon Bears, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - PAWS Bear Club- Manchester, UK, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - P'town Bears, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Orsi Italiani- Milan (Girth and Mirth), 1994-1999 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Oz Bears, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Ozark Mountain Bears, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Red Earth Bears (Oklahoma), 1995, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Redwood Empire Bears, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Rhode Island Grizzlies, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - River Bears (Cincinnati), 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Sacramento Valley Bears, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Show Me Bears- St. Louis, MO, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - South Bay Bears, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Southern Bears, 1993-2000 (Box 10, Folder 51-52)
  - South Florida Bears Growl-O-Gram, 1994-2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Steel City Centurions, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Susquehanna Valley Bears, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Swiss Bears, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Teddy Bear Leather Club of Virginia, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tidewater Bears Tidewater Times, 1993-1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tri-City Bears, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ursus (Dayton, OH) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Valley Bears, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Viking Bears, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Volunteer Bears (Knoxville TN), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - West Florida Growlers, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Wichita Bears, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Wombats (W. Australia), 1994-1999 (Box 11, Folder 14-16)
  - Woof Watch, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Yukon Mining Co. Providence, RI, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Bear Mailing List, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Bear Digests v.11 60-219, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 20-32)
  - Bears Digests v.12 1-119, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 33-44)
  - Bears Digests v.12 120-239, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1-12)
  - Bears Digests v.12 240-279, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
  - Bears Digests v.13 1-48, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5-9)
  - Bears List- Misc., 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Monty Bear Archives Compiled by Les Wright. Photos and fliers in blue binder, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Monty Bear Archives Compiled by Les Wright. Photos and fliers in blue binder, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Bear Expo '92, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Bear Expo '92 "What is a Bear?" workshop, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Bear Expo '93, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Bear Expo '93 workshop, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Bear Expo '94, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Bear Expo '95 (cancelled), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - International Bear Rendevous, 1995-2003 (Box 21, Folder 38-45)
  - International Bear Rendezvous 2002, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - EBMC (European Big Men's Convergence), Brussels, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Lazy Bear Weekend VI, July 2001 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Provincetown Bear Week, July 2001 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Bear Games 2001, Providence, RI, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Texas Bear Round Up, April 2002 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - DCBC (DC Bear Club) Bear Invasion, Bear Icons IV, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - American Indians/Native Americans, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Apollo Network, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Archives, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Backdoor BBS (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Bears 101" Lecture and Slide Show, Univ. of Connecticut, Storrs, February 2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Bear Club Handbook Formation, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Bear Codes- Steve Dyer, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Bear History: Personal Accounts, 1993-1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Bear Hug/Leather Bears (parties) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Bear Lecture for UMass, Amherst, November 2001 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Bear Necessities III, Indianapolis, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Bear.Net, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "Bear Quay", David Hooker, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Bears: Personal Ads, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Bear Web Ring: Joseph Alex Martin, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Bear websites, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Berenstain Bears, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - BML: Alex Schell, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Brush Creek Media (Bear magazine), 2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Bulmer, Darren (MancerBear), 2001 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Coleman, Joe, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Curtis, A.B. (children's stories) (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Folsom Street Fair, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Global Wrestling Alliance, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Guide to the Collection: The Heritage of the Community (BHP) by John Noble, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Hanky Codes, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Haskins, Edward Thomas Jr.: "What Is A Bear?" (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - INSIDE Bear Magazine, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Leather, 1989-1998 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Leather Navigator, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Library Reading by Les Wright in Tampa, FL, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - BHP Misc. (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - National March on Washington '93 Bear Contingent, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - New York City (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - "Paddleboro"/Attleborro, MA sex arrests, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Policarpio, Joe, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - San Francisco (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - torquere Bear History article, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Verisimilitude 2, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Verisimilitude 4, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Washington, DC Bearfest '94, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Anatolian Bear (Turkey), "Fred Trust" (Box 28)
  - Bare Bears of Maine (Box 28)
  - Bay State Bears (Massachusetts) (Box 28)
  - Beach Cities Bears (Box 28)
  - Bear Buddies Toronto (Box 28)
  - Bears' Club U.K. (Box 28)
  - Bears Cologne (Box 28)
  - Bears LA (Box 28)
  - Bears of Albany (New York) (Box 28)
  - Bears of Athens (Greece) (Box 28)
  - Bears of the Old Pueblo (Tucson, Arizona) (Box 28)
  - Bears of San Francisco (Box 28)
  - Bears of South Florida (Box 28)
  - Bears on the Bayou (Box 28)
  - Bears Ventura Growler (Box 28)
  - Berkshire Bears (Box 28)
  - Bi Bears (Box 28)
  - Bluegrass Bears (Box 28)
  - Boston Gen X (Box 28)
  - BrisBears (Australia), 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Cleveland Bears (Box 28)
  - Dallas/Fort Worth Big Men's Club (Box 28)
  - East Coast Bear (Canadian Maritimes) (Box 28)
  - Empire Bears (Rochester, New York) (Box 28)
  - Epicentro Ursino Romano, "Warbear" (Box 28)
  - Front Range Bears (Box 28)
  - Gay Bears Encounter in Madrid, 1999 (Box 28)
  - Great Canadian Bear Hunt Weekend, 1999 (Box 28)
  - Great Lakes Bears/Chicago (Box 28)
  - Green Mountain Growlers (Vermont) (Box 28)
  - Harbour City Bears (Box 28)
  - Hillside Campgrounds (Box 28)
  - Houston Area Bears (Box 28)
  - Lazy Bear Weekend, Castrobear Presents (Box 28)
  - Long Island Bears (Box 28)
  - Mannheim Bears/Mannheimer Bären Treff (Box 28)
  - Mid-Michigan Bears (Box 28)
  - Montreal Bears (Box 28)
  - Monty Bears (Box 28)
  - Monty Harvest Fest, 2001 (Box 28)
  - Mountain State Bears (West Virginia) (Box 28)
  - New England Bears (Box 28)
  - North Country Bears (Box 28)
  - Northeast Ursamen, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Oregon Bears (Box 28)
  - Pittsburgh Bears (Pennsylvania) (Box 28)
  - Prison City Bears (Box 28)
  - Provincetown ("P'town") Bears (Box 28)
  - Redwood Empire Bears (Sonoma County, California), 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Rhode Island Grizzlies (Box 31)
  - Rural Gay Men (Box 31)
  - Saskatoon Bear, Chubs and Chasers (Box 31)
  - South Bay Bears (Box 31)
  - Southern Bears (Atlanta) (Box 31)
  - Turkish Bears (Box 31)
  - VicBears (Australia) (Box 31)
  - Viking Bears (Stockholm, Sweden) (Box 31)
  - West Florida Growlers (Tampa, Florida) (Box 31)
  - Summer Bear Week, 2002 (Box 31)
  - Folsom Street Fair, 1998-2000 (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and articles (Box 31)
  - The Alley Bar (Box 31)
  - Bear Icons
    - Rogue Bears' Gallery (Box 29)
    - Retired correspondence (Box 29)
    - Background: gay art and photography (Box 29)
    - Leslie-Lohman Gay Art Foundation (Box 29)
    - Tours (Box 29)
    - Grants, underwriting, funding (Box 29)
    - Bear Icons (Box 29)
    - Alive with Pride! Chicago, August 2001 (Box 29)
    - New York City show, April 1999 (Box 29)
    - Exhibition catalog (Box 29)
    - BI2 performance artists (Box 29)
    - BI2 media contacts (Box 29)
    - BI2/BI3 multimedia (Box 29)
    - Boston (Box 29)
    - Mount Ida College: Jeri Goetz, Nancy McNeely, and others (Box 29)
    - Boston, gallery book information (Box 29)
    - BI2 press release, publicity, reviews (Box 29)
    - BI2 volunteers (Box 29)
    - Bear Icons 2 catalog (master) (Box 29)
    - Bears Icons and Beyond (Provincetown), gallery book originals (Box 29)
    - Bear Icons III-Provincetown, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Bear Icons 4-Provincetown, 2002 (Box 29)
    - Provincetown, artists' mailing, May 9, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Bear Icons 4-Baltimore/Washington, DC/DCBC invasion (Box 29)
    - Philadelphia, May 14-16, 2004, Bears on Liberty weekend (Box 29)
    - Tasty: Nashoba Collection at Burlington, Vermont, December 6, 2003 (Box 29)
    - London, June 1999 (Box 29)
    - Bear History Project version 3, News, September 2000 (Box 29)
    - Bear History Project version 3, correspondence (Box 29)
    - International Bear Rendezvous, 2004 (Box 29)
    - Bear Icons and Beyond...An Evolving Exhibition, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Bear Icon Artists
      - Adams, Jim (Box 29)
      - Allen (Box 29)